《L}律》前情提要
Previously on Better Call Saul...
跟我ff他怕的事
Tell me about the electricity.
我知道起砗茈x奇 但@是真的
- I know how it sounds but it's real.
我F在要去接那司C 如果他J得你 事情就不妙了
I'm picking up that driver. And if he knows you, that's bad.
警察]把@件事在案
The cops keeping it out of the papers.
你打算警察去找赫克托的麻
You wanted to put the cops onto Hector.
-他完全不得你了 -我可得他
- He forgot all about you. - I haven't forgotten him.
_塞拉大街1216 斯科茨代市 利桑那州
1216 Rosella Drive, Scottsdale, Arizona.
我]有e
This was no mistake.
他Я宋
He sabotaged me.
得我 你得回答不得
Remember me? The answer is no.
我知道他磉^ 我知道是他做的
I know he was here. I know what he did.
布m迪爸爸去了小Y拜堂
Father Brady's in the chapel.
如果你想他就按呼叫I
Just push the call button if you want to see him.
你上次吃|西是什Nr候
When was the last time you ate?
什N
What?
吃|西
Food.
你最近有]有吃|西
Have you had any lately?
我]事
I'm fine.
查克 我去Z槟前
Come on, Chuck, let's go over to Novi's
伸展一下手_ 呼吸一下空 吃c三明治
and stretch our legs, get some air, couple of hoagies.
F在@r候你想吃三明治
You want to get a sandwich? Now?
只是ff
Just a thought.
得那次我不小心邀了
Remember that time I accidentally invited
P西和x莉的@喜派
Kathy and Cheryl to Mom's surprise party?
那些地板的舞蹈幼魍好玩的
It was, kind of, tricky out on the dance floor.
那天晚上挺_心的
It was a fun night.
我只得大家後矶家忙著收拾你的子
I just remember the whole family cleaning up after you.
x_了自己的生日派
And Mom leaving her own birthday party
就榱蓑把其中一人送回家
to drive one of them home.
f真的 查克 我得吃c
Seriously, Chuck, we got to eat.
著 我x_一也不有事的
Look, Mom will be okay for a few minutes.
已三天了 可能我要在@呆上三天
It's been three days, it could be three more.
行
Okay?
走吧 哥
Let's go, buddy.
吉米 如果你想吃 你就去吃
Jimmy. You want to eat? Go eat.
我o你c
I'll bring you something.
烤牛排 不要番茄 意大利式
Roast beef, no tomato, Italian on the side?
行 R上回
Okay. Be right back.
Mom?
吉米
Jimmy.
不  我是查克
No. Mom. It's me Chuck.
吉米
Jimmy.
不  我是
No, Mom. It's...
所以她就@N走了
So this is it, then?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我已o她打^柔美t素了
She's has the DNR.
你弟弟在@Y
Is your brother in the building?
我可以用炔客ㄓ系y呼叫他
We can use the intercom.
不
No.
查斯
Charles.
你想我打找l
Is there anyone you want us to call?
]有
No.
嘿
Hey!
Hey...
查克 嘿 查克
Chuck! Hey, Chuck!
查克 在哪 怎N了
Chuck, where's Mom? What happened?
她去世了
She's gone.
什N 什Nr候
What? When...
怎N
How did...
她醒^ f了什N
Did she wake up? Did she say anything?
]有
No.
打o911
Call 911.
快打o911
Call 911!
W尼 x_@
Ernie, get out here!
嘿 你到底在做什N 嘿
Hey, what the hell are you doing? Hey.
明天斫o你半r
Come back tomorrow, it will be half-price.
是的 我需要救o
Yeah, I need an ambulance.
-我有l生 -很好
- I got paper towels. - Good.
流血了 拿什N托住他的^
...and now there's blood. Something for his head.
o我一|子|住他的^
Give me a cushion for his head.
好的 等下 等一下
Yeah, hold on... Hold on one second.
查克 e 跟我f
Chuck. Come on, come on.
恩
Yeah.
查克 嘿 嘿 嘿
Chuck. Hey, hey. Hey.
嘿 查克 你得到我f
Hey, Chuck, you with us buddy?
通中心 查克
The copy center. Chuck.
戈登街615
615 Gold.
夥 你好
Buddy, you okay?
不 他色看起聿话l{
No, he doesn't look blue.
嘿
Hey.
我很快把你送去t院 好 m斯
We're gonna get you to the hospital, okay? Lance...
-一切有我 -我在@工作
- Everything will be all right. - I work here.
e 查斯 R上就到了
Hang tight, Charles, we're almost there.
心c
Watch yourself.
_
Coming through.
档饺
On three.
一 二 三
One, two, three.
D移
Transferring.
查斯・吉 50多q
This is Charles McGill, late 50s.
他在打印店厥
He had a syncopal episode in a print shop,
lT看到了
witnessed by an employee.
估一分适б庾R
Estimated loss of consciousness is one minute.
各器官指撕芊定
His vitals are stable.
他前~有口
He's got a laceration to
需要p合
his forehead that appears to need suturing.
查斯 今晚稚读
Charles, how're you doing tonight?
-能和我f -是dBl作
- Can you talk to me? - Seizure activity?
D移r]有蟾嫔弦]有
Not in the transfer and none reported.
]有尿失禁
No urinary incontinence.
他有H人在@
Do we have any family members?
他弟弟在等候室
There's a brother in the waiting room.
你o他注射多少液w了
How much fluid did you give him?
-@是第一管 -艄
- That's the first liter. - Lights...
你想f什N 查斯
What's that, Charles?
你得把@絷P了
You have to turn off the lights.
-不 我F在不能@N做 H鄣 -上帝啊
No. We can't do that right now, sweetie. God...
你摔倒了^部 我得o你做些y
You fell and hit your head. We're gonna need to do some tests.
不 不 我得_著舨拍湍
No. No. We need the lights on to help you.
查斯 你能捏一下我的手
Charles, can you squeeze my hand?
用拍
Really hard.
The lights...
那又是啥
What is that?
]啥 我在z查你的氧庠O 查斯
Okay. We're just checking your oxygen there, Charles.
-你有^敏Y -]有
Do you have any allergies? No.
你有在吃
Are you on any medications?
]有
No.
好的 我F在要幽愕母觳埠屯
Okay, I'm going to move your arms and legs...
如果你X得疼了就告V我
...and you tell me if there's any pain.
-那就很疼 -看得到心D
- That just hurt. - Did we get an EKG?
什N
The what?
先生 心D有反
Gentlemen, did we get an EKG?
F在o她N五片
He's on a five-lead now.
我]有十二片的吧 ]有
We didn't get a twelve-lead. No.
好的 崔西 去找一下十二片的
Okay, Tricia, we're gonna need a twelve-lead.
不要心D 不要
No EKG! No EKG.
好的 查斯 我得做心D
Yes, Charles. We need to do an EKG.
-不 你不懂 我有特殊情r -查斯
No! You don't understand. I have a condition. CHARLES...
我非常^敏
I have a hypersensitivity to electricity.
查斯 用你的_抵著我的手
Charles, please push your feet against my hands.
很好 _保你的心K正常
Very good. ...to make sure your heart's all right.
不 你不能碰@
No, you can't touch this.
-我有特殊情r -崔西 能o我c光
I have a condition. Tricia, can I get a light?
我]同意你@N做
I did not give you my consent.
-你o噙@N做 -你不能碰@
You have no right to do this. You can't touch this.
-我得Oy你的心K -把@拿_
We need to monitor your heart. Get these out of here.
放p好 查斯
Just relax. Charles?
把絷P掉 拜
Turn the lights out, please!
冷o 查斯
Just stay calm, Charles.
查斯 你得配合我
Charles, you need to cooperate with us.
@很 我只要
This is gonna be very easy, we're just gonna...
抽一c血 p合好口
Draw a little bit of blood, suture up your wound,
再做一很蔚呙
and do a very simple CAT scan.
不要 不要做呙
No! No CAT scan!
-冷o -不要做呙
Calm! No CAT scan!
崔西 控制住他
Tricia, can we please get some restraints?
-小伙子 ^ -你不懂
Gentlemen, please come in here. You don't understand!
摁住他 克制住他
Can you hold him down. Restrain him.
P掉 查斯
Please turn off the lights. Charles.
你不能逼我
You can't make me...
冷o 查斯
Calm down, Charles.
我很快就弄好
We're just gonna get everything figured out for you.
固定住了 保持^部放低
We got you. Just keep your head down.
弗Y斯特t生 艽1821
Dr. Forest, dial 1821, please.
弗Y斯特t生 艽
Dr. Forest, please dial...
他怎N恿
How's he doing?
我也希望能告V你
I'd love to be able to tell you,
但在做那些y之前 我也不_定情r怎
but we can't know for sure until we do those tests.
你知道我要f什N
You know what I'm going to say.
恩 你不能做些常z查
Well, can't you just go old-school?
你知道的 z查他的瞳孔
You know, look at his pupils,
用\器看 那拥氖
use a stethoscope, that kind of thing?
他不想留在@
He doesn't want to be here.
他想要做什N和他需要做什N是
What he wants and what he needs
杉不同的事 吉米
are two very different things, Jimmy.
我不知道他失去意R是
We don't know if he lost consciousness
因樾呐K有P的}或因橐淮屋p度中L
because of a heart-related issue or if it was a mild stroke.
我不知道他的脊柱有]有受^害
We don't know if his spine has been injured,
他的大X是否[
if his brain is swelling.
他很可能X震U @是最保守的估了
He likely has a concussion at least.
查克再一次拒^了@些y
Chuck is once again refusing these tests
因檫@些可能他「受n舻挠绊」
because they involve "Being bombarded by electricity."
他f的
His words.
他上次倪@出去後 情rK]有多少改善
Nothing is changed since the last time he was in here.
著 我不知道怎N跟你f@
Look, I don't know how to explain this...
我]有答λ
I'm not committing him.
走Rr急救Oo行
What about a Temporary Emergency Guardianship?
我意思是 他符合
I mean, he fits the parameters.
你跟我f他需要o急t理
You're telling me he's in need of medical care so urgent
等不到法庭程序
that we can't wait around on court procedures.
最重要的是
Most certainly.
查克o法理解@幼
And Chuck is not able to understand
有什N後果
the consequences.
恩 其他是知道的 但他
I mean, he can understand them, but he...
然 法官也@NJ
Absolutely. A judge will see it that way, too.
我把他Щ丶胰会徇@一切就都Y束了
And then I take him home and it's over?
直到出Y果 有一些m的o理 然可以了
Pending results and proper treatment, yes.
我JR一F在就可以M的法官
I know a judge we can call right now.
我砀嬖V他
Let me be the one to tell him.
嘿 哥 感X怎N
Hey, buddy? How's it going?
查克
Chuck?
哇哦 @不是趁我病拿我Y料的人
Well, if it isn't Johnny-On-The-Spot.
什N 那是什N意思
What? What does that mean?
W人雇性
Is Ernesto out there?
恩 我能湍阕鳇c什N
Yeah. Can I get you something?
W人雇 快M xx
Come in here, please.
放p
Just take it easy.
W人雇
Ernesto!
把你|西放那
Just put your stuff in there.
我把他砹
I got him.
你感X怎N 吉先生
How are you feeling, Mr. McGill?
W人雇 我在打印店昏迷了多Lrg
Ernesto, how long was I unconscious in that print shop?
我不_定
I'm not sure.
30秒 1分 2分
Thirty seconds? A minute? Two minutes?
我X得大概1分吧
I'd say maybe about a minute?
你 有c 神志不清
You were, kind of, in and out.
那在救o碇前
And how long was I lying
我在地上躺了多久
on the floor before the ambulance arrived?
大概10分 我想 但我]看表
About 10 minutes, I think. But I didn't look at the clock.
而你也在那
And yet you were there.
查克 咱能不能
Chuck, can we...
你能那N快到那褐挥幸解
There's only one way you could have gotten there so quickly.
就是你根本就]有x_
You never left.
我X得你有c太^於咄咄逼人了
I think you're getting all wound-up.
做深呼吸放pc
Can you just take a few deep breaths?
你收I了他
You bribed him!
那後面的孩子 什N
That kid behind the counter. What?
在W人雇须x_之後和我到_之前
Between the time Ernesto left and I arrived,
你收I了那蠢蛋 他l誓f
you paid that half-wit to swear...
-^]有看^你 -吉先生
...he'd never laid eyes on you. Mr. McGill?
然後你就躲在一旁 偷偷看著
Then you stuck around. To watch.
槭颤N
Why?
-你就是想看我y受 -吉先生
Just wanted to see me suffer? Mr. McGill?
就是想嘲笑我@幅鬼幼
Just wanted to have a laugh at my expense?
是我叫他淼
I called him.
什N
What?
在^斫幽阒前 我o吉米打了
I called Jimmy earlier, before I picked you up.
他在你出事的r候出F 是因槲医o他打了
He showed up when he did because I called him.
我很心你 所以就
I was worried about you, and I just...
o他打了 我很抱歉
I called him. I'm sorry.
出去
Get out.
你z都出去
Both of you.
查克 我有些事必要做
Chuck, there's something that I have to do.
有我非常抱歉
And I'm really sorry.
我
I'm...
由衷地感到抱歉 但我必得@N做
...really, truly sorry, but I got to do it.
@是槟愫
And it's for you.
你想把我交oe人看管
You're trying to have me committed.
不 那只是Rr的
No, it's a temporary...
Rro急Oo @又有什N^e呢
Temporary Emergency Guardianship. Tomato, to-mahto.
最後你是F了初的想法
You've finally got me where you want me.
嘿 你看起碓阃噶
Hey. You look beat.
回去休息吧
Why don't you go home and get some sleep.
我留在@]} 只要他需要我
I'm fine to hang out. You know, whatever you need.
不 @]事了
Nah, we're good here.
嘿 W尼
Hey, Ernie.
你怎N想到fo我打的
How come you said that about calling me?
我不知道 夥
I don't know, man.
著 我其什N都不想f
Look, I didn't want to say anything,
但你哥哥 他最近起你的口吻
but your brother, the way he's been talking about you lately,
好像 δ愫懿M似的 吉米
it's like, he's really out to get you, Jimmy.
有 我也不知道 你是我的朋友
And... I don't know... You're my friend.
xx
Thanks.
我明天o你打
I'll call you tomorrow.
我想念]件收l室
I miss the mail room.
你知道希波克拉底誓言
Are you familiar with the Hippocratic Oath?
你了解了解
You should be.
v史上最古老的契s文件之一
One of the oldest binding documents in history.
意思是「先者o害」
"First do no harm."
我的情r不能@又委
This is not the way to treat my condition.
@就好像我ΡP尼西林^敏
It's as though I had an allergy to penicillin,
而你s猿钟盟碇委我的感染一
and yet you persist on treating my infection with it.
你的比很有趣 查斯
I appreciate the analogy, Charles,
但我不X得@比m合F在的情r
but I don't think it quite fits.
我在你a生不m之前
We'll have you in and out
做完放射治 好
of radiology before you know it, all right?
然後我再看看能不能把你的i圈取了
Then we can see about getting that neck collar off
你到DD
and get you moving around.
好了 查斯 F在_始呙
Okay, Charles, the scan is starting now.
你躺的桌子移
The table that you're on is going to move.
你到一些音 δ碚f可能有c大
You're going to hear a sound that might seem loud to you,
但是不用心
but it's nothing to worry about.
你做的很好 查斯 值煤
You're doing good, Charles. Good job.
我R上就Y束了
We're almost finished.
好了 希墒且27q身w健康的怪胎 她喜g普雷斯D
Okay. Heather is a 27-year-old fitness freak who loved Preston
K公_承J把自己看作是一行走的X包
but openly admits to thinking of him as a walking wallet.
是]消息
Still no word?
老天 @z查要花多Lrg
Jesus, how long is this gonna take?
她f全部的zy差不多要十分
She said the whole test would be, like, 10 minutes.
也S他得重^_始
Maybe they had to start over.
怎N 重二十遍
What, 20 times?
他呆在家Y
He should be home.
吉米 你做的是Φ
Jimmy, you're doing the right thing.
非常m她奢侈的生活方式
...very accustomed to her wealthy way of life.
所以 是l做的
So, who did it?
你可以去忙你的工作 拜
Would you get your work out, please?
因椴恢道我得在@捍舳嗑
Because God knows how much longer we're gonna be here.
如果你能做一些不那Nв嗅t院庀⒌氖虑 我
I'd feel better if you were doing something, you know,
感X好c
unhospitaly.
不в嗅t院庀
Unhospitaly?
我@就做
I'm on it.
博格曼先生 博格曼先生
Mr. Bergman? Mr. Bergman?
他是普雷斯D的律
That was Preston's lawyer.
他f他知道是l\⒘怂
He says he thinks he knows who killed him.
@影 我要去下最新M展
You know what? I'm going to go ask for an update.
好的 好主意
Okay. Yeah, good idea.
你是最棒的一代
You are the greatest generation.
吉米 看 二K非因你_始
Jimmy. Look. You didn't start World War II,
但_是因你Y束
but you sure as heck finished it.
如果@不
And if that weren't enough,
你⒁恢三百英尺高的火箭 送上了月球
you sent a rocket, 300 feet tall, to the moon.
F在 在你的S金r代
Now, in your golden years,
你需要有人照看你
you need someone looking out for you,
某你能信任的人
someone you can trust,
一言出必行 言行一致
a man who says what he does
的男人
and does what he says.
你需要依某人r
When you need someone to count on...
我要吉米
Give me Jimmy.
因槿缃袢烁窳α肯喈短缺啊
Because moxie is in such short supply these days.
吉米・吉 一你可以信任的律
Jimmy McGill... A lawyer you can trust.
真的很不e 吉米
It's really good, Jimmy.
你拍的V告相好
You made a really good commercial.
xx
Thanks.
吉米
Jimmy.
噢 K於Y束了 他怎N恿
Oh, finally. So, how is he?
好消息是 纳眢w上f 他挺好
Well, the good news is that, physically, he's okay.
放射科t生f 查斯的^和脊椎
The radiologist said everything looks normal
看起硪磺姓常
with Charles' head and spine,
所以我摘了i托
so we took his neck collar off.
他^上的K合也不e
His head wound will heal just fine.
我o他Я艘会
We gave him a tenus shot
因樗最近]有做作免疫接N
because his immunization records were not current.
我保C不δ阌幸馔
I'm sure that's no surprise to you.
有 有 他的心K呢
And... And... And his heart?
很
Strong.
心D正常
The EKG was normal.
至於失去知X 我的想法是
As far as losing consciousness, my best guess is
查斯得了所^的激性昏厥
Charles had what's called a stress-related syncope.
基本上就是@恐l作
It's basically a panic attack,
但是]有中L或心K病的E象
but no signs of a stroke or cardiac event.
不^ 他出F了
However, there was...
KlY
a complication.
查克 嗨 老兄 是我
Chuck? Hey, buddy, it's me.
他f一切都]} 所以我你x_@Y
They said everything looks good, so let's get you outta here.
你X得怎
What do you say?
他怎N了
What's wrong with him?
不管你打了什N 效都已退了 是吧
Whatever you gave him should've worn off already, right?
我^察了小r
We watched him for several hours.
我甚至o了他逆D
We even gave him what's called a reversal agent.
所以f 然 o┳饔孟退了
So, yes, the sedative wore off.
-是e的原因 -什N原因
- This is something else. - What?
我J槭亲晕艺TУ木oYB
We think it's a state of self-induced catatonia.
"我" Y老是е"我"
"We"... always with the "We."
我J槭悄阕约赫J
I think it's you.
你是@病房Y唯一的t生
You're the only doctor in the room.
我J槟阌媚翘C器牧怂的大X
I think you fried his brain with that machine.
吉米
Jimmy.
抱歉 都是胡f八道
I'm sorry. This is bullshit.
吉米
Jimmy.
有呢
What next?
我第一次治查斯的r候 他也是同拥B
When I first treated Charles, he was in a similar state.
你X得呢
Wouldn't you agree?
我必不得不相信 他清醒^
I have to believe that it's just a matter of time
只是rg}
before he comes out of it.
rg}
Matter of time.
好的 我就在@Y等著
Fine, then. I'll wait right here.
糁凶 偏差1.5分
Shot left. 1.5 minutes.
管可以用多少
How many rounds've gone through the tube?
762型
For a 762?
用3500^]}
You can put 3,500 through it and never know.
取Q於射舻淖力
It's about how tight she shoots.
@一的座力就很大
And this one's tight as they come.
我要f 著射舴较蛴悬cL
I'd say there's a breeze picking up downrange.
你的管冷s了
Your barrel gonna be cold?
希望如此
Let's suppose so.
好吧 你最好把注意力放在射羯
Well, then, you'd better have paid attention to that shot.
呃 我最好
Uh-huh. I'd better have.
向右{整 1.5度
Adjusting right, 1.5 minutes.
l射
Send it.
中了
Hit.
正中靶心
Center hit.
我想你是]Q
I suggest you don't change up your ammo.
在用168格令的船尾空心
Stick with the 168 grain boat-tail hollow point...
如果是射裟o任何遮 倒]PS
if it's an open shot, that is.
F在 如果你要射穿厚玻璃窗
Now, if you got to shoot through a heavy window,
我建h你用180格令的
I'll up you to a 180.
不^你知道 你需要重新估算射袅
But as you know, you'll have to recalculate the shot.
168格令的就好
168 will do it.
缀凶
How many boxes?
就一盒
Just the one.
不用 免M送你
No, it's on the house.
最後一件事
Uh, one last thing.
o意冒犯
No offense.
]事
None taken.
噢
Ohh.
吉米 能o我c水
Jimmy, can I get some water?
查克 嗨 老兄 你醒了
Chuck. Hey, buddy, you're back with us.
你怎N
How you...
能o我倒c水
Can I get some water, please?
然 然 水
Yeah, yeah, water.
嗯
Mnh.
噢 靠 抱歉
Oh, shit. Sorry.
要c
Want some more?
嗯
Mm.
噢
Oh.
我最後得的事是
Last thing I remember
我被放M了一台C器Y
was that machine they put me in.
我昏迷了多Lrg了
How long was I out for?
20小r
Was... 20 hours.
我要做的下一件事就是 你x_@鬼地方
And next order of business... get you the hell outta here.
然後呢
Where to next?
然後就我去拉斯克塞斯的精神病院
Some insane asylum in Las Cruces?
某你可以把我藏起 但不e的地方是吧
Someplace you can really tuck me away, but good?
回家 查克 我你回家
Home, Chuck. You're going' home.
有 你的心K]}
Well, your heart's okay,
^上的也]}
and so is that crack on your head,
@是我最想知道的事
so that's all I wanted to know.
TEG的事呢
What about the T.E.G.?
「T」意思是「Rr」
The "T" Stands for "Temporary," Right?
你想去床上躺著
You wanna go to bed?
不 不 @Y @Y更隹煲稽c
No, no. It's... It's cooler down here.
你想喝c什N
What can I get you?
我可以o你泡杯茶 呃 好茶
I'll make you some tea... uh, the good stuff,
不是t院Y的那N褐色的水
not that brown water they have at the hospital.
我]事了
I'm fine.
我o你泡杯茶
I'll make you some tea.
吉米 不用
Jimmy. No.
就
Just...
你已M到任了
You've done your duty.
F在你可以走了
You can go now.
我才f得有c
That came out a bit harsh.
我f 我昏了很久 被t生又戳又刺的
Look, I've been zapped and poked and prodded,
F在我只想o一o
and now I just I wanna be left alone.
如果你的情r又糟糕
If things start going south for you again,
我要怎N知道
how am I even gonna know?
我]事 我保C
I'm fine. I promise.
看到了
See?
已感X好多了
Feeling better already.
我是f 我都]有@Y的匙 所以
I mean, I don't even have a key, so...
我能叫W尼回
Can I get Ernie back here?
至少我叫他回 行
Would you let me do that for you, at least?
你需要有人陪著你
You need someone looking' in on ya.
得吃啊 是不是
You gotta eat, right?
好的
All right.
放一c 查克
Feel better, Chuck.
拜
Por favor!
好的 我R上就理
All right, I will get right on that.
下一周早些r候 我湍理好
I should have it for you by early next week.
祝您愉快 柯林斯先生
You have yourself a wonderful day, Mr. Collins.
噢 到你了
Oh! There you go.
是的 上墨R
Yeah, get the sunglasses out.
光太亮了
It's very bright.
得保o好老私家商
Gotta protect the old' peepers.
你要
You gotta...
是的 看起砗
Yep, looking sharp.
太好了
Bingo.
呃 F在 再
Uh, bye-bye, now.
好的
Okay.
大家好 很抱歉你久等了
Folks, I'm sorry about the wait,
但是我o每位客舻年P注意味著
but the attention I give each client means
有r 有些事有一c延t
sometimes, things get a little... backed up.
呃 但是 我保C
Uh but I promise
按次序c你面
to get to each and every one of you in turn.
德x佐夫人 H鄣 我相信您就是下一
Mrs. DeShazo, my dear, I believe you're next.
不^首先 有人需要我兔Φ贡咖啡
But first, may I get anybody some coffee?
我可以跟你下
Can I talk to you?
呃 我去去就
Uh, excuse me one second.
我需要找一位接待T 就像昨天
We have got to get a receptionist... like, yesterday.
吉米 霍A德打了
Jimmy, Howard just called.
他f今天上午他一直在找你
He says he has been trying to reach you all morning.
告V他不要┠ o我留信息就好
So? Tell him to stop bothering you and leave me a message.
是查克的事
It's about Chuck.
很重要 他是@Nf的
It's important... That's all he'll say.
好的
Okay.
很不幸 我的助理告V我
Unfortunately, uh, my associate tells me
有人找我些法律事
I'm needed for some brief but pressing legal business.
我只要打就行
I just need to make one quick phone call.
呃 便 l要咖啡碇
Uh, in the meantime, who was it who wanted coffee?
是的 好的 ~ @位年p的女士湍倒咖啡
Yeah, okay, uh, this young lady will get you coffee...
有 有甜甜圈 如果剩的
and, also, doughnuts if there are any left.
我要咖啡 不要任何奶油
I want coffee, but I do not want cream.
嗨 朱莉 是我 回霍A德的
Hey, Julie, it's me, returning Howard's call.
好的
Yeah.
嗨 出什N事了
Hey, what's up?
吉米 我只有一}
Jimmy, I have just one question...
是你在搞鬼
Are you behind this?
我搞什N鬼
Am I behind what?
吉米 我正在忙
Jimmy, I'm kind of in the middle of something' right now.
-^涸 -不 不 不
- Come back later. - No, no, no.
e@ _T
Come on. Open the door.
我知道你槭颤N 我可以待赫
I know why you're here. We can discuss it later.
F在我在忙 再
Right now I'm busy. Goodbye.
你F在_心了
You happy now?
@硬恍 我是f我]有@Y的匙
It's not right... Me not having' a key to this place.
查克
Chuck?
查克 呃 出什N事了
So, Chuck... uh, what's up?
嗯
Um...
你在
You got a little, uh...
你在做什N工程
You got a little, uh, uh, project going' on?
呃 你想跟我fc什N
Uh, something you maybe wanna tell me about?
怎N 查克 告V我
What do you say Chuck? Clue me in?
@些是石膏和木板l做的
These walls are plaster and lath...
完全醪蛔olV
completely invisible to the radio spectrum.
完全]有保o作用
No protection at all...
我可能跟站在光dd的牧錾喜畈欢
I might as well be standing in the middle of a pasture.
我不知道之前是怎N想的
I don't know what I was thinking.
我早@N做
I should've done this from the start.
什N 你早做 用@
What, you should've done this, with the, uh...
看到了 我想@些相厚了 我想
See, I think these walls are pretty solid. I think...
我真正需要的是法拉第\（o屏蔽）
See, what I really need is a proper Faraday cage.
@才是我需要的
That's what I need.
我想我需要坐下 休息一下 老兄
I think we need to sit down, take a break, buddy.
行
Please?
e用@N高人一等的Z 吉米
Do not patronize me, Jimmy.
我]有 知道
I'm not crazy, all right?
什N 我]f^你了
What? I never said you were crazy.
那 你可能是累牧
That... You're probably exhausted,
你至诉@N多活嘛
a-and justifiably.
嗨 戆 嗨
Hey, come on. Hey.
就五分 然後^m
Five minutes, and then right back at it.
我]事
I'm fine.
戆 查克
Come on, Chuck.
休息一下
Just a break.
-小心 -我知道
- Careful. - I know.
噢
Ohh.
霍A德告V我 你HHMo了
Howard tells me you quit HHM.
我]有o
I didn't quit.
我退休了
I retired.
起砜刹皇沁@
That's not what it sounded like.
o怎 都挺意外的 你不X得
Regardless, it's kinda out of the blue, don't you think?
他很心你
He's worried about you.
他如重
He should be relieved.
如重 他槭颤N要如重
Relieved? Why would he be relieved?
你是他的左膀右臂
You're his Number One Guy.
]有你 整事账都要前功M
Without you, that whole place goes down the drain.
所以 你 你退休
So, you... you retired...
不是不在HHM干了 而是不做律了
not just from HHM, but the law?
@不好 查克
That's not good, Chuck.
法律 法律行I 需要你
The... The law... needs you.
得了吧
Just stop it.
你也需要它
And you need it.
到底是槭颤N 查克
What brought this on exactly, Chuck?
哈
Huh?
因樵谖倚难Y 你就是天生的律
'Cause I don't know what you are if you're not a lawyer.
嗨
Hey...
你]我G掉律碗
How are you gonna retire before you get me disbarred,
]把我s出城 你怎N能o呢
before you run me out of the town on a rail, huh?
我成槭羌已Y唯一可以姓吉的
I'll be the only McGill carrying the family name.
你不能用
You can't have that.
是因 你失去了梅_S德的案子
Is this... Cause you lost Mesa Verde?
那又怎 l在乎@
So what? Who cares?
嗨 如果你真的J
And, hey, if you truly do think
是我陷害了你
that I ratfucked you on that thing...
m然我]有 但是o如何
which I did not, but whatever...
你知道
well, you know what?
你生饬 那就行悠戆
You get mad! Take action!
不要躲在你的法拉第什N
Don't just hide out in your... your Faraday whatever...
什N鬼\子Y
your cage thing here.
不 你 你不能退休
No! You... No retirement for you!
等你99q的r候
When you're 99, you can drop dead
你可以在向C器人法官做KY述r死掉
giving closing arguments to JudgeBot 3000...
便f C器人法官也用
which will run on electricity, by the way.
@才是你的未 好
That's your future, okay?
-所以 -我
- So... - I...
我再也植涣诉@活了
I can't do the job anymore.
什N意思 你然值昧
What do you mean? Of course you can do the job.
我犯了e`
I made a mistake.
什Ne`
What mistake?
一 什N都不是的y行地址
A simple, nothing little bank address...
-把1261成了1216 -噢
- 1216 instead of 1261. - Oh.
我搞砸了
I screwed it up!
o客粼斐闪p失
I hurt the client.
完全氐赘阍伊
Blew it completely and utterly.
之後我 我怪罪於你
And then I blamed... And then I blamed you.
都怪死的流
It's this goddamned electricity!
我崩⒘ 把我的能力消耗]了
It's wearing me down! It's wearing down my faculties!
我的大X 我的思想 ^去
My brain... my mind... it used to be...
你知道 ^去]}
You know, it used to work!
F在再也不行了
And now it doesn't anymore.
因槲 有人受到了p失
Mnh. People got hurt because of me.
是r候Y束了
Time to end it.
那如果我告V你 你]有犯e呢
What if I told you you didn't make a mistake?
天哪 吉米 不要再捉弄我了
For Christ's sakes, Jimmy, stop humoring me.
不要再f任何事了
Stop trying to talk everything right.
嗯
Mnh.
_是我陷害了你
I ratfucked you.
是我值
It was me.
我@一手 尼克松都佩服
I would've made Nixon proud.
我把1261改成了1216
I changed 1261 to 1216.
是我值
It was me.
你的猜想都是Φ
It all went down exactly like you said...
我是f 完全正_
I mean, exactly.
我卧炝搜}印件
I doctored the copies.
我花X 商店的孩子fe
I paid the kid at the shop to lie for me.
真是人受不了
It is insane
每一都你猜α
how you got every detail exactly right.
@幽憧梢苑朋了 好
So you can relax, okay?
因槟愕拇竽X正在以百分之一千的功率
'Cause that brain of yours is chugging along
超速\行
at 1,000% efficiency.
你是在告V我真相
Are you telling the truth,
是榱税参课
or are you just trying to make me feel better?
我@Nf是榱税参磕
I am saying' it to make you feel better.
不然跟你f@些致
I sure as shit wouldn't be telling you otherwise.
但是 是的 @是真相
But, yes... It's the truth.
你做了@N多 是榱诵呷栉
You'd go to such lengths to humiliate me?
我是榱私
I did it for Kim!
她榱四孟旅匪_S德 直I心r血
What... She worked her butt off to get Mesa Verde
而你和霍A德sf坐一 喝著威士忌 得意地笑
while you and Howard sat around sipping scotch and chortling.
哈姆林 哈姆林 吉 直就是一群吝莨
Hamlin, Hamlin, McGill... More like Scrooge and Marley!
金得到梅_S德 而不是你 不是HHM
Kim deserves Mesa Verde... Not you, not HHM.
她A得的 她需要它
She earned it, and she needs it!
我@N做是榱退
I did it to help her,
但是 f我]有想到 害你@N深
but I... I honestly didn't think it would hurt you so bad.
我以槟阒f 「噢 天哪 我犯了e`」
I thought you'd just say, "Oh, crap, I made a mistake,"
然後一切照f 跟平常人一
and go on with your life, like a normal person!
但是 噢 不
But, oh, no!
我V心妄想
Wishful thinking!
那N 我能 呃 告V霍A德
So, can I, uh, tell Howard
你不o或者退休
you're not quitting or retiring or whatever?
我能把那些鬼|西上扯下
And can we take all this shit down off the walls?
我要打o霍A德
I'm gonna go call Howard.
吉米
Jimmy.
你意R到你承J了一重罪
You do realize you just confessed to a felony?
我想是吧
I guess.
但是你感X好多了
But you feel better, right?
而且 是你的f法和我的不一致
Besides, it's your word against mine.